[{"question": " hey, you guys! guess what? barry and mindy are getting a divorce!", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " wow!", "answer": "  what is the matter with you?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " no! barry and mindy.", "answer": " oh sorry, i hear divorce i immediately go to ross.  who-who&#146;s barry and mindy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " barry was the guy that i was almost married and mindy was my best friend.", "answer": " ohh-oh, wasn&#146;t he cheating on you with her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " yeah, but that just means that he was falling asleep on top of her instead of me.", "answer": " why did they get divorced?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " well, apparently she caught him cheating on her with someone else. isn&#146;t that sad?  god, could you imagine if i actually married him?! i mean how different would my life be?", "answer": " i know what you mean, i&#146;ve always wondered how different my life would be if-if i&#146;d never gotten divorced.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " which time?", "answer": " the first time! no seriously, imagine if carol hadn&#146;t realized she was a lesbian.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": "  i can&#146;t. i keep seeing it the good way.", "answer": " i&#146;d bet i&#146;d still be doing my kara-tay.  towards the end of our marriage i was doing a lot of kara-tay as a way of releasing the tension from y&#146;know, not doing anything else physical.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " maybe the problem was you were pronouncing it kara-tay.", "answer": " and what if i was still fat?  well, you wouldn&#146;t be dating me, that&#146;s for sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " sure i would!", "answer": "  oh yeah! come on! yeah right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " what, you guys really think that i&#146;m that shallow?", "answer": " no, i just think monica was that fat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " hey, imagine if i never got fired off days of our lives!  oh-hey, there&#146;s carol again!", "answer": " what if i had had the guts to quit my job? i&#146;d probably be writing for the new yorker, getting paid to be funny. but my job&#146;s fun too! i mean tomorrow, i-i don&#146;t have to wear a tie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " what if i had taken that job at merrill lynch?", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " merrill lynch?", "answer": " yeah, i had a massage client who worked there and-and he said i had a knack for stocks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " well why didn&#146;t you take the job?", "answer": " because at that time you see, i thought everything that rhymed was true. so i thought y&#146;know that if i&#146;d work with stocks, i&#146;d have to live in a box, and only eat lox, and have a pet fox.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " hey, do you guys think that if all those things happened, we&#146;d still hang out?", "answer": " this is where the opening credits are, but they&#146;re not the usual opening credits. oh no! these credits are based on the world that would have been created had all of the above actually happened. it starts out with all of them at the fountain sitting on the couch as fat monica runs up and sits on the arm of the couch, tilting the whole thing towards her. it then goes on to show rachel&#146;s still a shop-aholic and with barry. fat monica is sweating while cooking and dancing while eating a donut. phoebe as the wall street shark smoking while on two cell phones. then they&#146;re dancing in the fountain. joey entering as dr. drake remoray and meeting a groupie. chandler trying to write as a bird does its business on his shoulder and falling asleep while typing. ross doing some kara-tay and trying to get carol into bed. and finally, some more dancing in the fountain, them all flexing, and the turning out the lamp and shutting off all the lights bit from the first season. just remember one thing, this is an alternate universe. everything from every other episode doesn&#146;t apply, for instance, ross and rachel have no history. and in fact have not seen each other in years in this world.}", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": "  oh my god! rachel green?", "answer": "  rob tillman!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " no-no. it&#146;s-it&#146;s me, ross!", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m sorry. ross tillman.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " no, no-no, ross geller.", "answer": " ohh, of course monica&#146;s brother!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " yeah. right.", "answer": " wow! how are you?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " ohh! me too!", "answer": " is-isn&#146;t it the best?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " oh, it&#146;s the best!  so, umm how&#146;s monica?", "answer": " oh really, really great! yeah! a-actually she&#146;s right down the street, umm, do-do you know what? you should stop bye and say hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " ohh, i would love too.", "answer": " yeah? oh-oh, she&#146;d be so excited!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " ohh! okay!", "answer": " come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " oh wait, don&#146;t you have to pay for your,  busty ladies?", "answer": " no, it&#146;s okay. some-some kid asked me to pick it up for him, but i don&#146;t&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": "  oh yeah? okay.", "answer": "  okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " but! don&#146;t you have to give him his money back?", "answer": " uh-huh.  hey, here you go buddy. sorry, no porn for you.  okay, let&#146;s go see monica!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " so monica, still going out with dr. boring huh?", "answer": " he&#146;s not boring! he&#146;s just-he&#146;s just low key.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " thanks.", "answer": " yeah. y&#146;know, the hazelnut actually not a nut, it&#146;s a seed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": "  wow!!", "answer": " can anyone else name a well known seed that&#146;s been masquerading as a nut?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " oh no! what&#146;s the matter?", "answer": " oh i just got another rejection letter. they said my writing was funny, just not &quot;archie comic funny.&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " y&#146;know what honey? i got to get back to the hospital.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": "  okay.", "answer": " bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " was his question what&#146;s more boring than him?", "answer": " hey man, look sorry about that archie thing. do uh, do you need me to give you some money?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " hey, i may have no money, but i still have my pride.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " ehh.", "answer": " maybe joey doesn&#146;t have to give you the money, tv stars have assistants right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " that&#146;s an idea!  hey, if i hired an assistant, would-would you take money from her?", "answer": " no joey! chandler could be your assistant! see, he could answer all of your fan mail and stuff!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " that&#146;s great! that would be great! let&#146;s do that!", "answer": " i could use the money; it could give me time to write.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " oh right great! welcome aboard!", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " all right! now hey, i need to use the bathroom. since i don&#146;t need any assistance in there, take a break!", "answer": " all right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey phoebe! guess what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " joey just hired chandler to be his assistant!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " hey mon!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": "  oh my god! rachel!!   you look terrific!", "answer": " ohh, so do you! did you lose weight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " you are so sweet to notice! yes, i lost three and a half pounds!", "answer": " and, and uh, you-you remember my friend chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " oh yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " oh my god, sit down! sit down! how long as it been since we&#146;ve seen each other?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": "  1987, the day after christmas, at sean mcmahon&#146;s party. i played you one of my songs, y&#146;know interplanetary courtship ritual.", "answer": " oh yeah. right. so now, are&#151;do you, do you still do music?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " sometimes, you should come over  sometime! i&#146;ll play you one of my other&#133;", "answer": "  oh my god! joey tribbiani from days of our lives, just walked in here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " rach, he&#146;s a friend of ours.", "answer": "  you are friends with dr. drake remoray?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " well it&#146;s kinda hard to be friends with drake because of his busy schedule and the fact that he&#146;s not real.", "answer": "  hey-hey, or i could bring my keyboard over here sometime!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " he&#146;s coming over! he&#146;s coming over!", "answer": "  joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " ohhh!  no! this is my friend rachel, we went to high school together.", "answer": "  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": "  hi!", "answer": "  hi! i love you on that show! i watch you everyday! i mean, when you took out your own kidney to save your ex-wife even though she tired to kill you&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " well, it&#146;s always nice to meet the fans.", "answer": " ah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": "  she&#146;s not crazy is she?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " hang on! hang on! hang on!  go!! who&#146;s this?  oh okay, you&#146;re gonna like working for me. what&#146;s your name?  what kind of name is brendy? i&#133; whatever&#133; stop talking! all right, from now on your name is joan. you can pick your own last name.", "answer": "  hey there you are!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " uh-oh, it&#146;s my boss!", "answer": " all right, here&#146;s a list of things for you to do today. man, this going to be so great! thank you so much! all right, i got to go to work i&#146;m delivering twins today, but only one of them is mine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": "  drop off my dry cleaning. pick up my vitamins. teach me how to spell vitamins. wear in my new jeans.", "answer": "  you realize what you are don&#146;t you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " you&#146;re his bitch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": "  no-no!! no!!", "answer": "  oh wait! you didn&#146;t just sit on my kit-kats did you?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " no! there-there was a little, a little diff in the market and i lost 13 million dollars.", "answer": " but the kit-kats are all right?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " what am i gonna do?! what am i gonna do?! i can&#146;t call my office they&#146;ll kill me! i can&#146;t call my clients they&#146;ll kill themselves! great, now my chest hearts.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": "  my chest hurts! oh, and now i-i can&#146;t breathe.", "answer": " phoebe, are you having a heart attack?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " oh, if i were, would-would i have shooting pains up and down my left arm?", "answer": " yes!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " come on pheebs, it&#146;s not that bad! y&#146;know most people would be excited if they didn&#146;t have to work for a couple of weeks.", "answer": " most people don&#146;t like their jobs, i love my job! i have not been working for three hours and i&#146;m already going crazy. i miss joan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " honey, having a heart attack is nature&#146;s way of telling you to slow it down.", "answer": " i always thought having a heart attack was nature&#146;s way of telling you to die!  but you&#146;re not gonna die. i mean, you are going to die, but you&#146;re not gonna die today. i wish i was dead.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  so what&#146;s going on with you?", "answer": " well umm, i&#146;ve been doing a lot more of my kara-tay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " still going through that dry spell with carol?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " how long has it been since you had sex?", "answer": " well, last weekend&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " oh that&#146;s not so bad.", "answer": " &#133;will be two months&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " that is.", "answer": " &#133;since i stopped trying.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " maybe you need to spice things up a little.", "answer": " what-what do you mean?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " i don&#146;t know. you could tie her up, she could tie you up; you could eat stuff off each other&#133;", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " y&#146;know, dirty talk, m\u008fnage \u00e0 trois, toys&#133;", "answer": " wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " roll playing&#133; you could be the warden; she could be the prisoner. you could be the pirate; she could be the wench!", "answer": " okay, i think i got it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " sorry. so how&#146;s it going with joey?", "answer": " oh just great. he beeps me now with codes. one is, &quot;bring me food.&quot; two is, &quot;i&#146;m with a girl, bring us food.&quot; three is, &quot;i&#146;m lost and i can&#146;t find food.&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": "  hey! is uh, is she gonna be all right?", "answer": " yeah! she&#146;s right in there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " all right, and over there is brady&#146;s pub where i like to unwind after a long day of surgeoning.", "answer": " wow! this is so amazing! what else? what else?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " well, that is a large piece of television equipment.  and uh that is an old man! hey old man!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " all righty, what do you say we head back to my place?", "answer": "  wow! umm, y&#146;know, i-i would really love to, but i-i shouldn&#146;t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " why?  why can&#146;t the world stop turning, just for a moment? just for us?", "answer": "  isn&#146;t that a line from the show?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " uh, yeah but uh,  i may have said those things before but, i never truly meant them. until now.", "answer": " that&#146;s a line from the show too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " okay, you watch too much tv.", "answer": "  here you go joe, here&#146;s the freshly squeezed orange juice you asked for.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " i thought we talked about this. i don&#146;t like pulp. no pulp. pulp isn&#146;t juice. all juice, okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry, i guess i just like the pulp.", "answer": " oh my god, i&#146;m sorry, i&#146;m being so rude.  rachel, would like a soda or something? because chandler would run right out and get it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " yeah sure, iced tea would be great.", "answer": "  iced tea.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " okay, anything for you sir?", "answer": "  did i not just tell him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": "  yes, you did.", "answer": "  okay look, chandler, if this  you have got to listen!   you&#146;re gonna throw that juice at me, aren&#146;t ya?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " so honey, this morning was fun, huh? me hopping in on you in the shower there.", "answer": " yeah! and maybe someday we could get a place with two bathrooms.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " look carol umm, i was, i was thinking maybe uh, maybe we can spice things up a little.", "answer": " what do you mean?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " carol our sex life is&#151;it&#146;s just not working&#133;", "answer": "  dad!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " hey there little fella! hey, uh-hey, why don&#146;t we get some shoes on ya, huh? hey, why don&#146;t you show dad how you can put your shoes on, in your room! yay!!", "answer": " yay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " yay!  seriously, our sex life&#133; i was thinking, maybe i don&#146;t know, we could try some-some new things. y&#146;know? for fun?", "answer": " like what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " well i don&#146;t know umm,  what if we were too tie each other up?  umm, some people eat stuff off one another.  nah! umm, y&#146;know we-we could try dirty talk?  umm, we could, we could have a threesome.", "answer": "  i love that idea!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " who sold a story to archie comics?!", "answer": " oh my god! that&#146;s great! oh wow!  you&#146;re a published writer! i wish i had a present for you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " aww.", "answer": " wait a minute!  my last kit-kat bar!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " you wanna share it?", "answer": " okay!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": "  hey! hey chandler look, i know you&#146;re mad, but i just want to say i&#146;m sorry. i-i was a total jerk. completely o-over the line. uh, i just i hate pulp! y&#146;know? i mean, y&#146;know how monica feels about low fat mayonnaise?", "answer": " it&#146;s not mayonnaise!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " what&#146;s this?", "answer": " fresh squeezed orange juice, with pulp! just the way you like it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " hey joey, chandler sold a story to archie comics!", "answer": " oh my god! that&#146;s great! congratulations! what&#146;s the story?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " oh you wouldn&#146;t uh, care. it&#146;s just a stupid comic book story.", "answer": " are you kidding me?! i love archie! and the whole gang!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " well uh, archie needs money to fix his jalopy , uh but he doesn&#146;t want reggie to just give him the money. so reggie hires him as his assist&#151;as his butler. and then makes him do all these crazy things like bring him milkshakes that can&#146;t have lumps in them.", "answer": " wait a minute. that sounds a little familiar! did they already do that one? &#145;cause i think i read it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " oh mon, listen i have to ask! okay, joey tribbiani invited me back to his apartment, now does he do this with a lot of girls?", "answer": " yeah, a lot. a lot, a lot!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " ohh! and i&#146;m one of them!! wow! oh, i just cannot believe this! i mean, joey tribbiani!", "answer": " well, y&#146;know it&#146;s none of my business, but aren&#146;t you married?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " yeah. oh i just wish we could not be married for a little bit! y&#146;know i just wish we could be like on a break!", "answer": " well, you&#146;re not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " oh, it&#146;s so easy for you i mean, you&#146;re not married, you get to have sex with who ever you want!", "answer": " yeah i can!  and don&#146;t think i don&#146;t, because i do! i mean all the time, you betcha!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " monica. you&#146;ve, you&#146;ve done it right?", "answer": "  of course i have! what do you think, i&#146;m some 30 year old virgin?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " oh my god! you&#146;re a 30 year old virgin!", "answer": " say it louder, i don&#146;t think the guy all the way in the back heard you! guy all the way in the back: yeah, i heard it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " it&#146;s not like, i haven&#146;t any opportunities. i mean, y&#146;know, i&#146;m just waiting for the perfect guy. i&#146;m seeing this guy roger, all right? he&#146;s not perfect, but umm, i think maybe i should just get it over with. y&#146;know, give him my flower.", "answer": " oh my god!! do it!! honey, you&#146;ve waited long enough!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? you are right?!", "answer": " yes!! i mean sex does not have to be a big deal! there shouldn&#146;t be all this rules and restrictions! y&#146;know, people should be able to sleep with who ever they want, whenever&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " rachel! i&#146;m never gonna think it&#146;s okay for you to cheat on your husband!", "answer": " oh what do you know? virgin!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " phoebe, why is smoke coming out of the bathroom?!", "answer": " oh yeah, the doctor said that could be one of the side effects.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " phoebe! put that cigarette out!", "answer": " no! it&#146;s not a cigarette! the smoke is coming out of me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " put it out!!", "answer": " okay! okay!  i&#146;m so glad you&#146;re here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " come on.  i got it.", "answer": " oh, give it to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " i got it!", "answer": " give it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " was it my work? were they mad? was it jack? did he yell?!", "answer": " j-j-just relax, nobody yelled. jack just was calling to make sure that you were getting better.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " thank god.", "answer": "  yeah, she&#146;s fired.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " you&#146;ve done all you can dr. wesley. you have got to let her go.", "answer": " good-bye and god speed, hope brady.  dr. drake remoray: not so fast wesley!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": "  remoray! dr. drake remoray: that&#146;s right wesley! i just stopped by to say that, you&#146;re not a real doctor! and that woman&#146;s brain, is fine!", "answer": "  oh! thank god!  dr. drake remoray: hope! hope!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": "  drake! dr. drake remoray: you&#146;re not dying hope, you&#146;re gonna live a long, healthy life. with me.", "answer": " oh drake.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " okay!  here we go! okay!  hi, joey! it&#146;s rachel! umm, i am free tomorrow night. yeah, sure, sure i can bring some sandwiches. commercial break", "answer": " this is where part ii begins, which means this is now episode 616.}", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " so honey this uh, this threesome thing umm, i mean how-how are you gonna start to find&#133;", "answer": " ooh, actually i&#146;ve been making a list of all the women i know who might be into doing this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " yeah. ooh, and i know gail rosten is in there twice, but she is so&#133;", "answer": " oh, i know.  y&#146;know, just-just talking about it is getting me kinda&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " oh, me too.", "answer": " yeah? well, i-i think ben&#146;s asleep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " oh umm, y&#146;know i think it would be better if we just save it.", "answer": " yeah. right. save it. i can do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " hey, pheebs!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " hey, how&#146;s it going?", "answer": " well, i&#146;ve got to get out of this bed, i&#146;m going crazy here. crazy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": "  here you go sweetie.", "answer": " what the hell is this, herbal tea? i hate herbal tea!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " she doesn&#146;t know she was fired yet, does she?", "answer": " no, the doctors say it may kill her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " what are you two girls whispering about over there?!", "answer": "  but i think we should tell her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": " hey pheebs, maybe this whole heart attack thing is a sign, that-that you should start think about getting a different job.", "answer": " okay, what is this? a stupid contest? because we got a winner here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}, {"question": " listen phoebe, he&#146;s right. people are not supposed to have heart attacks at 31.", "answer": " i know! but if i didn&#146;t work there, what else would i do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}, {"question": " well, you used to like playing the guitar.", "answer": " yeah that was lucrative! smart like your brother!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 313, "asentId": 314}, {"question": " uh, what about y&#146;know the massage thing? that never gave you a heart attack.", "answer": " hmm, pulling in a salary in the high six figures or rubbing gross naked people for chump change&#151;ooh, what do i do?! what will i do?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 315, "asentId": 316}, {"question": " ohh, i mean it&#146;s just so realistic!", "answer": " i know.  yeah, his name is pat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 317, "asentId": 318}, {"question": "  do you uh, do you&#151;ready for a refill?", "answer": " oh, i probably shouldn&#146;t&#151;so i will!  oh! wow! it&#146;s like it&#146;s raining!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 321, "asentId": 322}, {"question": " pretty cool, huh? but if you&#146;re thinking you can put a fish in there and it wouldn&#146;t get sucked up into the mechanism, well you&#146;d be wrong.", "answer": " umm, can i use your bathroom?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 323, "asentId": 324}, {"question": " okay.  god y&#146;know, if someone told me a week ago that i would be peeing in joey tribbiani&#146;s apartment&#133;", "answer": " yeah, life&#146;s pretty great isn&#146;t it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 327, "asentId": 328}, {"question": " i hope you&#146;re hungry, we&#146;re starting with oysters. and y&#146;know what they say about oysters, don&#146;t you?", "answer": " they have parasites?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 331, "asentId": 332}, {"question": " no! umm well, some people say that oysters are an aphrodisiac.", "answer": " what people?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 333, "asentId": 334}, {"question": " so oysters, huh?", "answer": " and then we&#146;re gonna have a little middle eastern cous-cous. something we can eat, with our hands.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 337, "asentId": 338}, {"question": " y&#146;know, it&#146;s funny, but when we were studying communicable diseases&#133;", "answer": " no-no-no, no! it&#146;s sensual!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 339, "asentId": 340}, {"question": " ohh! didn&#146;t know! okay!", "answer": " okay!  ohhh no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 341, "asentId": 342}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry sweetie, it&#146;s the hospital. the food looks great, maybe save me some?", "answer": " i can&#146;t promise anything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 343, "asentId": 344}, {"question": " we&#146;re really gonna do this, huh?", "answer": " looks like it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 345, "asentId": 346}, {"question": "  i got it!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 349, "asentId": 350}, {"question": " thank you so much for coming.", "answer": " oh, i wouldn&#146;t miss it for the world.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 355, "asentId": 356}, {"question": " i&#146;m-i&#146;m ross by the way.", "answer": "  hello ross.  i love what you&#146;ve done with this space.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 357, "asentId": 358}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry you&#146;re here with me instead of roger.", "answer": " yeah, me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 363, "asentId": 364}, {"question": " stop it!! that&#146;s not funny!!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 367, "asentId": 368}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry, okay? it just&#151;tonight was supposed to be y&#146;know, it was supposed to be a big deal.", "answer": " what was tonight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 369, "asentId": 370}, {"question": " you don&#146;t want to know what tonight was.", "answer": " okay.  what was tonight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 371, "asentId": 372}, {"question": " well, tonight was&#151;was going to be my first time.", "answer": " with roger?  not just with roger?!  oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 373, "asentId": 374}, {"question": " all right relax mr. i&#146;ve had sex four times!", "answer": " four different women! i&#146;ve had sex way more times!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 375, "asentId": 376}, {"question": " how many?", "answer": " nine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 377, "asentId": 378}, {"question": " i was just waiting for the perfect guy.", "answer": " well good, good for you. you really think that roger is the perfect guy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 379, "asentId": 380}, {"question": " no. he&#146;s not a horrible guy.", "answer": " hey that&#146;s what i tell girls about me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 381, "asentId": 382}, {"question": " chandler, i&#146;m gonna die a virgin!", "answer": " no you are not! you are sweet and wonderful and this is gonna happen for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 383, "asentId": 384}, {"question": " oh really? when? do you wanna do it with me?", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 385, "asentId": 386}, {"question": " i was kidding.", "answer": " so was i.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 387, "asentId": 388}, {"question": " joey, you&#146;re such an amazing actor!  how do you know where dr. drake remoray leaves off and joey tribbiani begins?", "answer": " well, with dr. drake they always tell me what to say. and with joey, i pretty much have to make it up on my own.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 389, "asentId": 390}, {"question": " wow! tell me something joey&#151;&#151;whoa! i just fell right off the couch there.", "answer": " yeah you did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 391, "asentId": 392}, {"question": " here you go. let me ask you a question.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 395, "asentId": 396}, {"question": " when was the last time someone told you just how beautiful you are?", "answer": " wow! i can&#146;t, i can&#146;t feel my hands.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 397, "asentId": 398}, {"question": " we can&#146;t do this.", "answer": " no!  oyster?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 401, "asentId": 402}, {"question": " yeah!  if-if-if we did do this there would be a lot of pressure on me, y&#146;know? because you&#146;ve been waiting a very long time and i wouldn&#146;t want to disappoint you.", "answer": " yeah but see i have nothing to compare it too. so even if you&#146;re horrible, how would i know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 403, "asentId": 404}, {"question": " i do like that.", "answer": " it&#146;s harder for me! i have those four other women to compete with!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 405, "asentId": 406}, {"question": " well, if it helps there were only three. so it would just be for tonight, right?", "answer": " absolutely! it would just be one friend  helping out another friend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 407, "asentId": 408}, {"question": " stop it! we&#146;re doing this! let&#146;s do it!", "answer": " noo!! okay!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 409, "asentId": 410}, {"question": " umm, do you have any uhh, moves?", "answer": " i have some moves.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 413, "asentId": 414}, {"question": " i have no moves.  okay, whatcha doin&#146; there?!  oh y&#146;know what? i&#146;m sorry, this is just too weird.", "answer": " yeah, let&#146;s just forget it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 415, "asentId": 416}, {"question": " oh yeah.", "answer": " chandler?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 421, "asentId": 422}, {"question": "  yeah?", "answer": " that&#146;s the couch. commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 423, "asentId": 424}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " i know! i&#146;ll tell you something, we are gonna do that again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 425, "asentId": 426}, {"question": "  morning!", "answer": "  oh right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 429, "asentId": 430}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": "  oh god. oh i can&#146;t believe joey tribbiani heard me throw", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 431, "asentId": 432}, {"question": " well he actually saw you a little bit too.", "answer": " noo! oh god we did&#151;we didn&#146;t, we didn&#146;t uhh&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 433, "asentId": 434}, {"question": " no! no! no, not after seeing that.", "answer": " god i&#146;m just a horrible person.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 435, "asentId": 436}, {"question": " wh-why?", "answer": " because i&#146;m married. that&#146;s right, i am a married woman! and i came to a tv star&#146;s apartment to have an affair! uck!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 437, "asentId": 438}, {"question": " that&#146;s ridiculous! i&#146;m not a &quot;star,&quot; just a regular famous actor.", "answer": " yeah and i&#146;m a horrible, horrible person.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 439, "asentId": 440}, {"question": " rachel, would you stop saying that?! hey-hey look, remember on the show when-when caprice was dying and she gave me&#133;", "answer": " the ring from the cave, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 441, "asentId": 442}, {"question": "  oh my god, they let you keep that stuff?!", "answer": " sure! as long as they don&#146;t find out you can keep whatever you want! and i want you to have it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 445, "asentId": 446}, {"question": " no! no-no-no&#133;", "answer": " yes! yes!! and every time you look at it, i want you to remember that you are a good person. okay, you&#146;ve had the chance to cheat, and with me, but you didn&#146;t. and that&#146;s what this ring stands for.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 447, "asentId": 448}, {"question": " but i thought that ring stood for caprice&#146;s undying love for her brother.", "answer": " look, do you want the ring or not?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 449, "asentId": 450}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 453, "asentId": 454}, {"question": " look at you! you&#146;re up!", "answer": " all right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 455, "asentId": 456}, {"question": " i thought i&#146;d try to take a walk. would you pour me some water? i&#146;ll be back soon.", "answer": " whoa-whoa-whoa! you&#146;re not gonna use the pay phone to call work, are", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 457, "asentId": 458}, {"question": " hey joe did&#133; did you ever have a threesome?", "answer": "  well uh, look ross i uh, i think carol&#146;s great and i&#146;m sure you&#146;re a very attractive man, but i&#133;.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 463, "asentId": 464}, {"question": " no! the reason i&#146;m asking is that&#133; i sorta had one last night.", "answer": " you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 465, "asentId": 466}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 467, "asentId": 468}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " all right! so, was it amazing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 469, "asentId": 470}, {"question": " it was, it was okay.", "answer": " just okay&#151;did you do it right?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 471, "asentId": 472}, {"question": " look, it&#146;s just did, did you ever go to a party and think, &quot;would really anyone miss me if i weren&#146;t here?&quot;", "answer": " huh. but still ross, you&#146;re worst day with two women, pretty much better than any other day! y&#146;know what i mean?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 473, "asentId": 474}, {"question": " it&#146;s just, my part seemed to be over pretty quickly and then, and then there was a lot of waiting around.", "answer": " but you got to be with both of them, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 477, "asentId": 478}, {"question": " not-not really. th-th-there was just carol.", "answer": " not the other one?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 479, "asentId": 480}, {"question": " no, she kept kicking me away!", "answer": " yeah, you don&#146;t want that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 481, "asentId": 482}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " well hey, at least you got to see a lot of stuff, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 483, "asentId": 484}, {"question": " oh i a lot of stuff!", "answer": " you got a little bored?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 485, "asentId": 486}, {"question": " a little. yeah. i made a snack.", "answer": " yeah? what did ya have?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 487, "asentId": 488}, {"question": " just a sandwich. turkey, a little mustard&#133;", "answer": " sounds good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 489, "asentId": 490}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 493, "asentId": 494}, {"question": " let me tell you about this chick i scored with last night! oh no wait a minute that was you!", "answer": " hey, check me out, i&#146;m a slut!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 495, "asentId": 496}, {"question": " so you uh, want to do something tonight?", "answer": " oh i can&#146;t. dr. roger is coming over again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 497, "asentId": 498}, {"question": " are you okay?", "answer": " yeah! totally! totally, and you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 501, "asentId": 502}, {"question": " great! it&#146;s so amazing! i mean, last time dr. roger came over, i was so nervous, but then after being with you i&#146;m all like, &quot;can the doctor see me now?&quot;", "answer": " i bet he can.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 503, "asentId": 504}, {"question": " y&#146;know, i don&#146;t have an appointment, but i sure could use a physical.  are you sure you&#146;re okay?", "answer": " oh yeah! yeah! don&#146;t worry about me, i&#146;ll be fine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 505, "asentId": 506}, {"question": " ohh! my god! barry!!", "answer": " you-you-you said you were gonna be away all weekend!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 507, "asentId": 508}, {"question": " surprise! look who&#146;s back!", "answer": " hey pheebs!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 511, "asentId": 512}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": "  call security.  pheebs, didn&#146;t you get fired?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 513, "asentId": 514}, {"question": " uh, i don&#146;t think so!", "answer": " phoebe?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 515, "asentId": 516}, {"question": " jack!! hey!", "answer": " what are you doing here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 517, "asentId": 518}, {"question": " all better! back to work! except this clown from research told me i was fired. he should do his research, huh?", "answer": " well, you were fired.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 519, "asentId": 520}, {"question": " nu-uh!", "answer": " i told that guy who answered your phone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 521, "asentId": 522}, {"question": " oh, okay i didn&#146;t get that message. so this doesn&#146;t count&#151;anyway, i&#146;ll be in my office.", "answer": " uh, phoebe you-you don&#146;t have an office.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 523, "asentId": 524}, {"question": "  phoebe, listen&#133;", "answer": " you&#146;re in my office! look, i have made a lot of cash for this company! okay? i am talking big bucks! pesos! yen! rubles! you make one little mistake&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 527, "asentId": 528}, {"question": " you lost 13 million dollars.", "answer": " oh, so this is all about money! y&#146;know it&#146;s bad enough that&#151;ow! oh, you have got to be kidding!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 529, "asentId": 530}, {"question": " are you all right?", "answer": " i&#146;m having another heart attack!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 531, "asentId": 532}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " i&#146;m having another heart attack!! call 9-1-1!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 533, "asentId": 534}, {"question": "  dumbass!", "answer": " hey pheebs! how&#146;s it going?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 537, "asentId": 538}, {"question": " well, they fired me and i&#146;m having heart attack.", "answer": " wow! well, welcome back!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 539, "asentId": 540}, {"question": " hi ross!", "answer": " hey rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 543, "asentId": 544}, {"question": " is joey tribbiani here?", "answer": " umm, no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 545, "asentId": 546}, {"question": " well, if you see him, will you please tell him that i&#146;m looking for him and that this i am not gonna throw up!", "answer": " that-that&#146;s always good news. are you okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 547, "asentId": 548}, {"question": " me? i&#146;m great! i&#146;m fine! i&#146;m sooo good!! but, you know who&#146;s not great?! men! you&#146;re a man right ross?!", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 549, "asentId": 550}, {"question": " sit down!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 551, "asentId": 552}, {"question": " let me uh, let me ask you something, do wedding vows mean squat to you people?! and why is it that the second we tell you we&#146;re going out of town, bamn there you are in bed with the neighbor&#146;s dog walker?!", "answer": " we&#146;re sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 553, "asentId": 554}, {"question": " no seriously! seriously! what has happened to the sanctity of marriage?", "answer": " didn&#146;t you spend last night at joey&#146;s?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 555, "asentId": 556}, {"question": " aw what are you?! a detective?", "answer": " look i-i don&#146;t know what&#146;s going on with you and your husband and what is hopefully an adult dog walker, look can i just say not all men are like that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 557, "asentId": 558}, {"question": " hey! there are some men who will do whatever it takes to make their marriage work! okay? there are some men who will stand by and-and watch as their wives engage in-in what only can be described as a twosome with some-some woman she barely knows from the gym!", "answer": " who are these men?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 561, "asentId": 562}, {"question": " men. i guy i know.", "answer": " well, you might want to tell him it sounds like his wife is  gay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 563, "asentId": 564}, {"question": " she is not&#133;  she&#146;s gay. oh my god. she is so gay! i can&#146;t believe this.", "answer": " good day for married people huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 565, "asentId": 566}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry your husband cheated on you.", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry your wife is gay. i guess women aren&#146;t that great either.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 567, "asentId": 568}, {"question": "  okay to come in?", "answer": " yeah, come on, eat, whatever you want. dr. roger got beeped again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 571, "asentId": 572}, {"question": " yeah i know, guess who beeped him?", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 573, "asentId": 574}, {"question": " why would you do that?", "answer": " because you shouldn&#146;t be with him.  you should be with", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 577, "asentId": 578}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah! when you were talking about roger, that was killing me! look, things like last night they don&#146;t just happen. y&#146;know? or at least not to me. or with the other two women, in the morning y&#146;know i was just lying there and i couldn&#146;t wait to just go hang out with my friends, but with you i always y&#146;know with a friend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 579, "asentId": 580}, {"question": " chandler!", "answer": " i know you probably don&#146;t want to go out with me, y&#146;know because i make too many jokes and i&#146;ve never been in a serious relationship and i guess i&#146;m not technically a &quot;doctor&#133;&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 581, "asentId": 582}, {"question": " there was just one woman, wasn&#146;t there?", "answer": " no, there were two.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 583, "asentId": 584}, {"question": " including me?", "answer": " oh yeah. ending credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 585, "asentId": 586}]